Paweł Kaleta

Email: pawel.krzysztof.kaleta@gmail.com

Tel: 695-610-731 Dwelling-place: Pruszków

PERSONAL PROFILE

PORTFOLIO

An ambitious, conscientious, self-motivated, eager-to-learn tester and a self-thought programmer with analytical prowess. Ready to combine engine architectural design insight and scripted tools development skills achieved through personal side projects with almost 5 years of AAA experience in QA to help empower game-dev veterans on the journey of creating amazing worlds and compelling stories.

SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

- testing methodologies and practices
- programming (C++)
- game engine architecture
- understanding of a game's performance and optimization techniques
- hardware and software testing tools

- zeal to learn and the ability to do so quickly
- analytical and holistic thinking habit
- delight and pursuit of progress and improvement
- effective and respectful communication
- sense of responsibility for the project
- identification with the team

Languages: Polish – native, English – B2 (upper-intermediate)

Familiarity with: game/level design, popular game engines, C#, JS, Agile, Scrum and VCS workflows, Git

WORK EXPERIENCE

09.2019 - date Lionbridge Poland

QA Tester (Minecraft Bedrock Edition)

- Testing: daily BVTs, smoke tests, cross-platform and platform-specific scenarios, in-game purchases, RC and branch integration passes, post-release verifications, bug scrubs, playtest feedback based investigations, performance, regression and compatibility testing; platforms: PC, Xbox, PS4, mobiles
- Technical investigating of bugs: deducing root causes, acquiring crash dumps, callstacks, debug logs and platform-specific event logs, capturing profiling and networking data, bisecting commits
- Bug reporting, tracking, updating and linking with other work items in the database (Azure DevOps)
- Creating test documentation, reporting collective test results, providing feedback for developers, proposing improvements for testing procedures and practices

2015 – 2018 Decathlon sp. z o. o. (organization unit - store Decathlon Okecie)

• 2017 – 2018 Trainer of Sales • 2016 – 2018 Brand Ambassador • 2015 – 2018 Salesman

2016 – 2017 Student Council at Faculty of Management of Warsaw University of Technology

EDUCATION

Computer Science part-time 1st-degree engineering studies at Warsaw School of Computer Science

2017 – 2020

Management extramural 1st-degree studies at Warsaw University of Technology

2016 - 2017

Matex XIV High School of Stanisław Staszic in Warsaw, class profile with an experimental

2012 – 2015 program of teaching mathematics for students especially talented and extended range

of teaching physics and computer science

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

works of J. R. R. Tolkien, pop culture, manga/anime